Gizelle v.Z. JUNIOR FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Current student undertaking a full-stack web-development bootcamp, seeking to gain industry experience following course completion in August 2021.

Creative personality with a passion for the arts. Former practicing lawyer with several years of experience in criminal and civil law.

PROJECTS

Portfolio website (HTML, CSS)

Riddles

Terminal application (Ruby): Riddles is a colourful game that runs from the shell and accepts user input.

Artize

Marketplace (Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, Bootstrap, Devise, Cloudinary, Stripe): Artize is an online gallery to buy and sell art.

Arcade Secretary

Teamwork Hackathon Challenge (JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS): Arcade Secretary is a score-based speed typing game.

EXPERIENCE

Case Manager

Health sector September 2018 – July 2020

Solicitor

Civil law, plaintiff, litigation November 2017 – August 2018

Solicitor

Civil law, plaintiff August 2016 – October 2017

Lawyer

Criminal law February 2014 – August 2016

Paralegal

Inquiries January 2013 – February 2014

Legal Secretary & Receptionist

Business, corporate, conveyancing February 2010 - February 2011

PRIVACY

*A detailed resume is available on request.



CONTACT



https://github.com/Ellezique



https://www.linkedin.com/in/gizellevz/

TECH STACK

HTML

JavaScript

PostgreSQL

CSS RUBY React

RAILS

TOOLS

VS Code GitHub Netlify Heroku

Trello

Cloudinary

Diagrams.net Balsamic Stripe pgAdmin

Wireframes

Wireframes

EDUCATION

Diploma of Information Technology

2020 - Current (Anticipated August 2021)

Graduate Diploma of Legal Practice 2012 – 2013

Bachelor of Laws (Second Class Honours) 2010 – 2012

Certificate III Business Administration (Legal) 2012